[Music]
and I'll help you hi yeah I'm calling I
rented a car from you guys yesterday but
I am actually coming because the man who
assisted me I felt like there was some
vibes and I just I just wanted to call
and see maybe if I could you know
connect do you remember
helping me yesterday no I don't
unfortunately if it's you I'm gonna go
nuts yeah I wasn't even working
yesterday I mean I kinda now that we're
talking I kinda wish you were working
yesterday remember what they looked like
um he was really handsome a kind of a
dimple on one side okay and I don't
remember seeing a wedding ring okay well
if you want to give me your phone number
wait would I be giving you my phone
number like for for them yes or for you
for them we can talk in code if you if
we have to are you are there other
people around you can't really like tell
me their story possibly yes
say escalator if there's someone
listening you can't say exactly what you
want to say I'll I got a couple other
people here if you if you want to leave
me your phone number I can more than
happily give it to the person I make me
able to help you tomorrow so you want my
number
sure yes you do yes escalator you want
it okay yes all right get that pen ready
baby hey okay ready it's four eight zero
six six five
wait someone's listening to me now
escalator yeah no I'm gonna be right
back
uh-huh my boss he has such a crush on me
do you have that yeah Oliver all the
time right
it's like that's not cool all right what
look I get I got a couple other
customers here okay me too okay I'll
transfer your number tomorrow okay what
was your first name again my name is
Cheryl brandish okay and I'm also
available ish and I work at the mattress
okay you know the one there's like uh
yeah across the highway it has an
inflatable gorilla on the roof you kind
of can't miss it's the flagship God
what's your name again Carlos Carlos
keep killing it escalator all right
escalators all right say it Carlos
escalator I love you too okay
[Music]